{
    "id": "ea351f8a9b2d4afeb3d9a808c6e52c5b",
    "title": "Such And So",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You are ……………………… baby.",
            "description": "We use such before a noun with or without an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "such a",
                "such",
                "so",
                "so a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1117d7f9f5ca43aba00a27f9318315a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am surprised that you have ………………….. patience.",
            "description": "We use such before abstract nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6e027f487044e2793921e34d06ea063"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………… beautiful.",
            "description": "We use so before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b00c6519b5e04ecd8b04cd2c7fc5095b"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are …………………….. idiots.",
            "description": "We use such before plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such an",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8e32ab466b5a4547be99bef30ed4ce0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got ……………………….. bizarre habits.",
            "description": "We use such before plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f50c9a99af014744a9692f61208fa246"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never met …………………….. beautiful woman.",
            "description": "We use such a before a singular countable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0c4aade010d5483b81eaed1fed5f9273"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………… childish.",
            "description": "Before adjectives, we use so.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "669373a74ff04c709eb6029b92caed29"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got ………………………. crazy ideas.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b7fa3833bdc47d7bb23533864ae28d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………………. intelligent.",
            "description": "We use so before adjectives.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such an",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0b13dd938a464eb29bba1f4e9c640715"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was …………………….. loud noise that it woke everybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "92621e2b14d94f56a9e45b6644b9473e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am glad that you are feeling …………………… better.",
            "description": "We cannot use so before a comparative adjective. Instead, we use so much.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a63681d2a95d46ce8779dbbbf9ddc9eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have got ………………………. to do.",
            "description": "We can use much or so much before an infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "so much",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b06195f66e8d4ba996c83f82f5f33183"
        }
    ]
}